ACTWU Newsclipping Files regarding J.P. Stevens Boycott 5744
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Clothing Union Resurfaces as Pacesetter on New Frontiers, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 83)
  The Washington Post. May 30, 1978
- Long Dispute Between Union, Stevens Is Discussed By Speakers, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 84)
  Statesville Record and Landmark. May 31, 1978
- Fight Against Stevens Revives ACTWU As Leading Labor Force, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 85)
  The Greenville News. June 2, 1978
- Controversy Erupts At Martin Processing, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 86)
  Franklin News Post. June 8, 1978
- Court Denies Martin's Attempt To Avoid Testimony In Lawsuit, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 87)
  Martinsville Bulletin. June 8, 1978
- Union President Attacks Textile Firm, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 88)
  Las Vegas Review-Journal. June 8, 1978
- Brown-Lung Curb Faces Cost Cutback, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 89)
  The Washington Post. June 8, 1978
- Textile Officials Back Holland Import Bill, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 90)
  Columbia State. June 11, 1978
- Another Side of the Stevens Tale, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 91)
  Playground News. June 10, 1978
- Dispite Thick Thumbs, Midge Hangs On in West Wing, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 92)
  New Times. June 12, 1978
- Getting Away With It, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 93)
  Afro American Tribune. June 13, 1978
- Black Textile and Apparel Workers in South Severly Affected by Textile Imports, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 94)
  Oklahoma Eagle. June 15, 1978
- Officials of Boycotted Firm Defend Labor Practices, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 95)
  The Hartford Courant. June 15, 1978
- Black Employment In South Hard Hit By Imports Of Textiles, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 96)
  Baton Rouge Community Leader. June 15, 1978
- Tariff-Cut Foes To Hold News Conference, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 97)
  Daily News Record. June 16, 1978
- Trade Agreements Affect Everyone: The Impact of Exports and Imports, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 98)
  The Washington Post. June 17, 1978
- After some infighting over their cost, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 99)
  Burrelle's TV Clips. June 20, 1978
- Group Avoids Stevens Stand, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 100)
  The Greenville News. June 20, 1978
- Pressure on Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 101)
  Washington American and The Washington Tribune. June 20, 1978
- ACTW Talking Merger With Shoe Workers, 1978; News clipping (Box 6, Folder 102)
  Daily News Record. June 21, 1978
- Pressure on Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Baltimore Afro American. June 24, 1978
- Textile Import Curb Sought, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Elberton Star. June 30, 1978
- U.S. Textile Industry Seeks Import Curbs, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Philadelphia Inquirer. June 30, 1978
- Textilists and Labor Unite, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 4)
  The Charlotte Observer. June 30, 1978
- Textile Import Curb Sought, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 5)
  The Atlanta Constitution. June 30, 1978
- Business, Labor Seek to Limit Textile Imports, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 6)
  The Washington Post. June 30, 1978
- Curb Textile Imports, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 7)
  The Chicago Sun-Times. June 30, 1978
- Makers, Unions Unite: Textile Parties Urge Halt To Import Rise, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 8)
  June 30, 1978.
- Compromise Standard for Cotton Dust Is Unveiled, Attacked, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 9)
  The Washington Post. June 20, 1978
- City Backs Stevens Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Dayton Journal Herald. June 1, 1978
- A Giant Step:' Ponder Won't Be Patsy On Stevens' Board, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Columbia Record. June 2, 1978
- ACTWU Trips To Stevens Plants Blasted, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Reception Pleases Union Reps Visiting J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Spartanburg Journal. June 6, 1978
- The Stakes Are High: J. P. Stevens vs. Union, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 14)
  The News and Observer. June 11, 1978
- 2 Churches Refuse To Boycott Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Some Union Boycotts Have Impact, But Most Of Them Flop, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Florida Food and Grocery News. July 1978
- Adversaries United In Import Fight, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 17)
  The Birmingham News. July 2, 1978
- United Action for Textiles, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 18)
  The Greenville News. July 2, 1978
- Industry-Labor Leaders Make Plea, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Southern Textile News. July 3, 1978
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Cincinnati to Rule On Stevens' Buys, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Allied Industrial Worker. July 1978
  - Item 2: The Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union will begin a national campaign, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Lenoir News-Topic. August 1, 1978
  - Item 3: Contract Renewed For Skill Training, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 20)
    AFL-CIO News. July 29, 1978
- Textile Men Call For Federal Aid In Cutting Imports, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 21)
  Chemical Marketing Reporter. July 3, 1978
- Textiles Under Attack, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 22)
  Youngstown Vindicator. July 4, 1978
- Textiles and Protection, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 23)
  The News and Observer. July 5, 1978
- Furor Over Textiles, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 24)
  Chemical Week. July 5, 1978
- Stevens Side, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 25)
  Crawfordsville Journal and Review. July 6, 1978
- Stevens' Deal Called No Solution, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 26)
- He's Waiting For The Man!, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 27)
  Kentucky Labor News. July 8, 1978
- Who Won Not The Real Issue, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 28)
  Laurinburg Exchange. July 21, 1978
- MYOB, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 29)
  July 15, 1978.
- Hardy Amies, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 30)
  Daily News. July 25, 1978
- Stevens Told To Let Up, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 31)
  The Fayetteville Observer. July 26, 1978
- The Issue Is Social Justice Says Union Representative, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 32)
  Ambler Gazette. July 27, 1978
- J. P. Stevens Agrees To Leave Union Alone, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 33)
  The News and Observer. July 27, 1978
- Union Harrassment Hist Below Belt, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 34)
  Greenville News-Piedmont. July 30, 1978
- International Boycott of Firm's Goods Urged, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 35)
  Vancouver Province. August 1, 1978
- Stevens Loses Atlanta Boycott Suit, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 36)
  The Charlotte Observer. August 3, 1978
- Is The Union Trying To Isolate J. P. Stevens?, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 37)
  Textile World. August 8, 1978
- J. P. Stevens in Easthampton, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 38)
  Valley Advocate. August 16, 1978
- Complaint Accuses Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 39)
  Winston-Salem Journal. August 18, 1978
- NLRB: Skip Election At Four Stevens Plants, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 40)
  The News and Observer. August 24, 1978
- Textile Firm Warns Dukakis On Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 41)
  Boston Sunday Globe. August 6, 1978
- Stevens Boycott Rally Planned, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 42)
  The Nashville Banner. August 22, 1978
- Union Formulating Worker's March On J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 43)
  The Tennessean. August 23, 1978
- Stevens Tactics Pose Threat To Others, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 44)
  The News and Observer. August 31, 1978
- Court Ruling Upholds Stevens Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 45)
  Labor World. August 31, 1978
- Human Rights Issues and J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 46)
  Response. September 1978
- Commend Levitt's Sale Of J. P. Stevens Stock, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 47)
  Civil Service Leader. September 1, 1978
- Ray Rogers Will Get You If You Don't Watch Out, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 48)
  New Englander. September 1978
- Labor Is Fastest Growing Owner Of U.S. Industry, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 49)
  Rapid City Journal. September 3, 1978
- On Labor Day, a look at one of the country's longest running and roughest union disputes, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 50)
  Burrelle's TV Clips: David Brinkley. September 4, 1978
- New Labor Muscle, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 51)
  Montgomery Advertiser. September 4, 1978
- Back Pay Check, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 52)
  September 6, 1978.
- Catholic Leaders Urge Boycott of J. P. Stevens Co., 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 53)
  The Washington Post. September 7, 1978
- Tough Ruling Against Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 54)
  Northern California Labor. September 8, 1978
- Church Joins Union Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 55)
  Philadelphia Daily News. September 8, 1978
- Shirt Maker and Union Agree on a 3-Year Pact, Averting Walkout Today, 1976; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 56)
  The New York Times. September 9, 1978
- 180 Urge J. P. Stevens Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 57)
  The Tennessean. September 10, 1978
- Two Articles from The Washington Star., 1977; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Even The Tablecloths Caused Problems At Labor Convention, 1977; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 58)
    The Washington Star. September 10, 1978
  - Item 2: Where The Labor Law Doesn't Apply, 1977; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 58)
- New Union Assault On J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 59)
  Newsday. September 12, 1978
- Union Seen Forcing Split on Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 60)
  New York Daily Press. September 13, 1978
- Corporate Campaign' Gains Against Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 61)
  AFL-CIO News. September 16, 1978
- Computer Loses One To Textile Whiz Kids, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 62)
  The Boston Globe. September 16, 1978
- Director Resigns at Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 63)
  The Washington Post. September 13, 1978
- Union Forces Stevens Board Change, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 64)
  Newsday. September 13, 1978
- Finley Bows to Union, Leaves NY. Life, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 65)
  Daily News Record. September 13, 1978
- N.Y. Life Co. Next Target In Anti-Stevens Campaign, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 66)
  The Washington Post.. September 12, 1978
- Union Drive In Mill Town: A Southern Community Divided, 1977; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 67)
  The Record. September 12, 1977
- Union Puts Heat On N.Y. Life in Stevens Fight, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 68)
  Daily News Record. September 12, 1978
- Textile Workers Union Tries to Harass New York Life in Fight With J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 69)
  The Wall Street Journal. September 12, 1978
- The Recidivist, 1977; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 70)
  The New Republic. September 17, 1978
- Insurance Executive Quits J. P. Stevens Board, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 71)
  Union Advocate. September 18, 1978
- Dismantling Stevens' Interlocks, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 72)
  Berkshire Eagle. September 19, 1978
- "Great" Ideas Dept., 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 73)
  Advance Star. September 21, 1978
- Making It Even Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 74)
  Environmental Action. September 23, 1978
- Meany Proposes 2-Level Price Index to Help Poor, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 75)
  The Los Angeles Times. September 26, 1978
- Most Union Chiefs Still Standing By Carter, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 76)
  The Los Angeles Times. September 27, 1978
- Five Articles from various newspapers, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: "Great" Ideas Dept., 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 77)
    Orange Shopper. September 26, 1978
  - Item 2: A Change In Labor Practices, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 77)
    Douglas Progress. September 27, 1978
  - Item 3: Quick Quiz, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Item 4: Workers: Union Efforts, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 77)
    Badger Enterprise. October 14, 1978
  - Item 5: Workers: Union Efforts, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 77)
    New Hampton Tribune. October 19, 1978
- Labor and J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 78)
  Torrington Register. September 27, 1978
- A Long Battle at the Mills, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 79)
  Discipline. September 17, 1978
- Unions Stepping Up Stevens Fight, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 80)
  The Record. September 19, 1978
- Brown Woos Labor As Younger Gives Policy, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 81)
  Imperial Valley Press. September 28, 1978
- Brown Links Human Rights to World Labor Standards, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 82)
  Valley News and Valley Green Street. September 28, 1978
- Brown Woos Labor With 10 Bills, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 83)
  Los Angeles Herald Examiner. September 28, 1978
- Four Articles from various newspapers., 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: "Great" Ideas Dept., 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 84)
    Drumright Journal. September 5, 1978
  - Item 2: Are You Fair-Minded?, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 84)
    Bladen Journal. October 5, 1978
  - Item 3: Are You Fair-Minded?, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 84)
    Drumright Journal. September 28, 1978
  - Item 4: Workers: Union Efforts, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 84)
    Robersonville Herald. October 4, 1978
- Brown Woos Labor Support, Backs Boycotts, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 85)
  The San Diego Union. September 28, 1978
- Catholic Leaders Endorse Boycott of J. P. Stevens Products, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 86)
  Galesburg Labor News. September 28, 1978
- Brown, Younger Woo Voters, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 87)
  Midway Driller. September 28, 1978
- Textile Workers Convene In L.A., 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 88)
  San Diego Daily Transcript. September 28, 1978
- Union Convention, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 89)
  Richmond Times-Dispatch. September 29, 1978
- Brown Woos Delegates to Textile Union Convention, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 90)
  Los Angeles Times. September 28, 1978
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Coretta Cites Record, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 91)
    The Houston Post. September 28, 1978
  - Item 2: Coretta For Bill, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 91)
    Waco Tribune-Herald. September 28, 1978
  - Item 3: Scores Jobs Bill Critics, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 91)
    The Atlanta Constitution. September 28, 1978
- Indigenous Music, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 92)
  Nation. September 30, 1978
- Two Part System Apparent Failure, Says Stetin: American Workers Should Give Thought To Setting Up A Third Party, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 93)
  The Chemical Worker. October 1978
- J. P. Stevens: Perpetual Motion, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 94)
  Retail Week. October 1, 1978
- Why Our Labor Laws Don't Work, 1977; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 95)
  MBA: Master in Business Administration. October 1, 1978
- A Kiss Does Not a Marriage Make, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 96)
  Textile World.October 1978
- Jerry and Jekyll, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 97)
  La Habra Star Progress. October 4, 1978
- Four Articles from various newspapers., 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: "Great" Ideas Dept., 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 98)
    Lake City News and Post. October 5, 1978
  - Item 2: Are You Fair-Minded?, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 98)
    Buffalo Press. September 27, 1978
  - Item 3: Who Fought Whom?, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 98)
    Opp News. September 7, 1978
  - Item 4: Who Fought Whom?, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 98)
    Opympia Review. October 4, 1978
- Textile Union Walks Out Over Wages, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 99)
  The Bergen Record. October 9, 1978
- Self-Interest, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 100)
  Fortune. October 9, 1978
- ACTWU Presses Boycott of Stevens, Seek Curbs On Low-Wage Imports, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 101)
  Galesburg Labor News. October 12, 1978
- Back Roads of the Mind, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 102)
  Real Paper. October 21, 1978
- Msgr. Higgins On Industry, Labor Unions, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 103)
  The National Catholic. October 22, 1978
- Six Articles from various newspapers, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Item 1: Are You Fair-Minded?, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 104)
    Branford News. September 21, 1978
  - Item 2: The most years worked by one person, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 104)
    Bridgeport Index. October 14, 1978
  - Item 3: Workers: Union Efforts, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 104)
    Cumberland Tri-City News. September 28, 1978
  - Item 4: Workers: Union Efforts, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 104)
    New Hampton Economist. October 3, 1978
  - Item 5: Workers: Union Efforts, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 104)
    Cedartown Standard. October 28, 1978
  - Item 6: Workers: Union Efforts, 1978; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 104)
    Springfield Herald. September 28, 1978
- J. P. Stevens and Co. Could Incur Stiff Fines For Labor Law Defiance, Court Asserts, 1977; News clipping (Box 7, Folder 105)
- Six Articles from various newspapers, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: "Great" Ideas Dept., 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Thousand Islands Sun. November 2, 1978
  - Item 2: One of the longest fights in labor history, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Nyrtle Point Herald. November 2, 1978
  - Item 3: Protecting America: Freedom Not To Join, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Southeastern Times. October 30, 1978
  - Item 4: Protecting America: Freedom Not To Join, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Castlewood Republican. October 5, 1978
  - Item 5: Workers: Union Efforts, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Daily Defender. November 11, 1978
  - Item 6: Workers: Union Efforts, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Union Says It'll Tackle J. P. Stevens Investors In Bitter 15-Year Fight, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 2)
  The Washington Star. November 7, 1978
- Clergy Aid Stevens Company Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 3)
  St. Louis Disciple. October 3, 1978
- Boycott of J. P. Stevens Involves Billions of $$$, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Cambridge Jeffersonian. October 12, 1978
- Hiring Quota for Stevens Overruled, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 5)
  The News and Observer. October 6, 1978
- Union Opens New Front Against J. P. Stevens, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 6)
  The Evening Sun. October 3, 1978
- Sander Genis: Labor History in a Small Round, Tough Packet, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Minneapolis Tribune. November 12, 1978
- ACTWU Pushing For Law to Slice Stevens Ties to Money Market, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Textile Week. November 13, 1978
- Low Investment Level Hurts U.S. Sales, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 9)
  St. Louis Post-Dispatch. November 14, 1978
- Imported Clothing: What Price to U.S., 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 10)
  The Detroit News. November 16, 1978
- Stevens Hearing: Who To Believe, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Martinsville Bulletin. November 19, 1978
- A Matter of Principle, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Columbus Ledger. November 12, 1978
- Stevens Director Vows To Stay Despite Union, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 13)
  The Washington Star. November 11, 1978
- J. P. Stevens Hearing Starts, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 14)
  Roanoke Times and World News. November 8, 1978
- NLRB Judge's Forecast: Stevens' Hearing May Last 6 Months, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 15)
  November 8, 1978.
- An Age of Limits: New Politics of Scarcity Poses Need for Fundamental Reforms, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 16)
  AFL-CIO News. November 25, 1978
- Corporate Profits Soar As Growth Rate Slackens, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Three Articles from various newspapers, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Campus Protesters: Back Again, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Camden Courier-Post. December 6, 1976
  - Item 2: Labor Women Back Stevens Boycott, Plan Nationwide Recruitment Drive, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Galesburg Labor News. November 4, 1976
  - Item 3: The textile workers' dipute, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Boston Pilot. November 26, 1976
- Church Official Backing Boycott, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 19)
  The Providence Journal. November 29, 1978
- J. P. Stevens and Co.: Symbol of Labor Strife, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 20)
  Bergem Record. November 26, 1978
- It's Petering Out, 1978; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 21)
  Wellsville Spectator. November 26, 1978
- Clothing Workers Begin J. P. Stevens Boycott, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 22)
  The Plain Dealer. December 7, 1976
- A Boycott Battle to Win the South, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 23)
  Business Week. December 6, 1976
- Nassau Students Protest Against Board Chairman, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 24)
  The Trentonian. December 6, 1976
- Two Articles from The Atlanta Constitution and the Princeton Town Topics., 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Repercussions of J. P. Stevens Boycott Reach Westcott Road as Brown's House Is Picketed, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Princeton Town Topics. December 9, 1976
  - Item 2: South Carolina: Lingering Recession, Low Pay Among Woes, 1977; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 25)
    The Atlanta Constitution. January 9, 1977
- Clothing Workers To Boycott Firm, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 26)
  The Evening Bulletin. December 8, 1976
- Plans for Boycott Of Stevens Made At Philly Session, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 27)
  Daily News Record. December 8, 1976
- Two Articles from The Miami Herald and the Rock Hill Herald, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Drive Zeroes In On Conditions At Textile Mills, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 28)
    The Miami Herald. December 19, 1976
  - Item 2: Textile Firm Silent On Boycott, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Rock Hill Herald. December 8, 1976
- Seven Articles from various newspapers, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Boycott of Textiles Advocated, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Boston Herald American. December 3, 1976
  - Item 2: Boycott Pending, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Belleville News-Democrat. November 29, 1976
  - Item 3: Stevens Boycott Is Continuing, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Daily News Record. December 7, 1976
  - Item 4: Stevens Charged, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Greenville Piedmont. November 29, 1976
  - Item 5: Union Boycott, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 29)
    New Orleans Times-Picayune. December 6, 1976
  - Item 6: Union Files Charges Against J. P. Stevens, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 29)
    The Wall Street Journal (san Francisco, CA). November 29, 1976
  - Item 7: Union Files Charges Against J. P. Stevens, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 29)
    The Wall Street Journal (Dallas, TX). November 29, 1976
- Textile Boycott Envisions Unionizing All the South, 1976; News clipping (Box 8, Folder 30)
  The Washington Post. December 5, 1976